<resources>
    <string name="app_name">t_3</string>
    <string name="search_main">Search weapon...</string>


    <array name="recycler_test">
        <item>name_weapons_1</item>
        <item>name_weapons_2</item>
        <item>name_weapons_3</item>
        <item>name_weapons_4</item>
        <item>name_weapons_5</item>
        <item>name_weapons_6</item>
        <item>name_weapons_7</item>
        <item>name_weapons_8</item>
        <item>name_weapons_9</item>
        <item>name_weapons_10</item>
        <item>name_weapons_11</item>
        <item>name_weapons_12</item>
        <item>name_weapons_13</item>

    </array>

    <array name="recycler_test2">
        <item>Калибр: 47.92 mm</item>
        <item>Калибр: 37.912</item>
        <item>Калибр: 27.192 мм</item>
        <item>Калибр: 17.92</item>
        <item>Калибр: 17.921</item>
        <item>Калибр: 87.922</item>
        <item>Калибр: 57.292</item>
        <item>Калибр: 47.92</item>
        <item>Калибр: 57.92</item>
        <item>Калибр: 74.92</item>
        <item>cal.44ggg55</item>
        <item>cal.445hhh45</item>
        <item>cal.4ttt5</item>
        <item>cal.4ffff5</item>
        <item>cal.4gfgg5</item>
        <item>cal.4hhhhh5</item>
    </array>


    <array name="splash_screen_text_content">
        <item>"The good people of this world are very far from being satisfied with each other and my arms are the best peacemakers."\n– Samuel Colt</item>
        <item>"Я не знаю, каким оружием будет вестись Третья мировая война, но Четвёртая — палками и камнями."\n– Альберт Эйнштейн "</item>
        <item>"С помощью доброго слова и пистолета вы можете добиться гораздо большего, чем только одним добрым словом."\n– Аль Капоне</item>
        <item>"Пули меняют власть быстрее, чем выборы."\n– Фильм "Оружейный барон" (Lord of War)</item>
        <item>"Главное правило торговца оружием — не быть застреленным из своего же товара"\n– Фильм "Оружейный барон" (Lord of War)</item>
        <item>"Тяжесть — это хорошо. Тяжесть — это надежно. Даже если не выстрелит, таким всегда можно дать по голове."\n– Фильм "Большой куш" (Snatch)</item>
        <item>"— Зачем тебе револьвер?\n— Чтобы научиться доверять людям."\n– Пауло Коэльо</item>
        <item>"Забавно, не так ли, что диаметр помады точно соответствует сорок пятому калибру?"\n– Алан Брэдли</item>
        <item>"Винтовка — это первое оружие, которым ты должна научиться пользоваться. Потому что оно держит тебя на почтительном расстоянии от клиента."\n– Фильм "Леон" (Léon)</item>
        <item>"…если у тебя есть винтовка, рано или поздно ты из нее выстрелишь.\n– Стивен Кинг"</item>
        <item>"— Ладно, кто ещё применяет винтовки калибра 0,308?\n— В Техасе? Охотники, охранники... домохозяйки..." \n– Сериал "Мыслить как преступник" (Criminal minds)</item>
        <item>"Более 550 миллионов единиц огнестрельного оружия находятся в обороте по всему миру. На 12 человек приходится одна пушка. Остается один вопрос: как вооружить остальных 11?"\n– Фильм "Оружейный барон" (Lord of War)</item>
        <item>"Если воюют торговцы оружием, боеприпасы никогда не кончаются."\n– Фильм "Оружейный барон" (Lord of War)</item>
        <item>"Револьвер — превосходный аргумент для джентльмена, который может завязать узлом стальную кочергу."\n– Arthur Conan Doyle</item>
        <item>"Над чем бы учёные ни работали, у них всё равно получается оружие."\n– Курт Воннегут</item>
        <item>"You can't say that civilization don't advance, however, for in every war they kill you in a new way."\n– Will Rogers</item>
        <item>"The only thing you should feel shooting someone is giving back."\n– StarCraft 2: Wings of Liberty</item>
        <item>"It’s a dangerous habit, Mr Holmes, to keep a loaded revolver in the pocket of your own robe"\n– Arthur Conan Doyle</item>
        <item>"Whoever comes to me with a sword is totally behind in the arms race."</item>
        <item>"God created men. Colonel Colt made them equal."\n– American proverb</item>
        <item>"… an armed society is a polite society. Manners are good when one may have to back up his acts with his life."\n– Robert Anson Heinlein</item>
        <item>"Guns don’t like jokes, they don’t forgive mistakes."\n– Inscriptions on firing ranges and weapons in the Soviet Army</item>
        <item>"As long as I have a pen in my hand and a gun in my pocket, I’m not afraid of anyone."\n– Benito Mussolini</item>
        <item>"With weapons, the law is silent."\n– Marcus Tullius Cicero</item>
        <item>"Prisons and morgues are full of idiots who thought with a gunshot wound in their pockets they could do anything."\n– Irvine Welsh</item>
        <item>"A weapon is not a dog. It doesn't matter if it’s a master or a villain."</item>
        <item>"There are no bad guns, there are bad shooters."\n– Marshal of the Soviet Union</item>
        <item>"Blame the user, blame the manufacturer, but don’t blame the gun."\n– David Mitchell</item>
        <item>"If you want to restrain the bad guys, arm the good guys!"\n– Anne Fortier</item>
        <item>"- Is it wise to give children a weapon?\n- I put a safety on it. What do you think I am?"\n– Lilyhammer</item>
        <item>"The sound of weapons drowns out the voice of law."\n– Michel de Montaigne</item>
        <item>"In two years... I’ve been taught that you need a head to go with a barrel. Brains."</item>
        <item>"You can’t have too many guns, you can’t have too many bullets."</item>
        <item>"The weapon you don’t know how to use is likely to be turned against you."\n– Kerstin Gier</item>
        <item>"One shot, one kill. That was the sniper's credo."</item>
        <item>"You can love a weapon, you can dislike it, but it’s always better to have it on you."</item>
        <item>"A weapon is really nothing without the man holding it."\n– Jodi Picoult</item>
        <item>"Democracy is two wolves and a lamb voting on what to have for lunch. Liberty is a well-armed lamb contesting the vote."\n– Benjamin Franklin</item>
        <item>"... women tend to handle guns better than men when they stop listening to ridicule."\n– Christopher Bunch</item>
        <item>"Whatever happens, we have got\nThe Maxim gun, and they have not."\n– Hilaire Belloc</item>
    </array>

</resources>
